ADAM SHERRILL

Austin, TX 78613

Phone: (512) 762-9400 | Email: adamsherrill2@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/adam-sherrill-5159a9244 | GitHub: https://github.com/ajsherrill2

Portfolio: https://ajsherrill2.github.io/AS-Developer-Portfolio

SUMMARY

Full Stack Junior web developer trained at the **University of Texas coding boot camp** with a certificate in full-stack, Front-end and Back-end web development. Determined app developer motivated by problem-solving; focusing on clean and modular back-end development. Strengths in responsiveness, increased productivity, effective communication, experienced in diverse project roles and leadership with strong interpersonal skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML5 | CSS3 | Javascript | ES6 | SQL | JSX

Frameworks/Libraries: Node.js | React.js | Express.js | JQuery | Bootstrap | Materialize

Databases: MySQL | Sequelize | MongoDB | Mongoose | MERN Stack

Tools/Concepts: Git | VS Code | Responsive Design | Rest API | MVC | ORM

Team Skills: Team collaboration, Agile development, Project demonstration/storytelling

PROJECTS

Daily Fit Nutrition | https://github.com/ajsherrill2/Project-2-Late-Night-Coders.git | https://daily-fit.herokuapp.com/

- Created a full stack calorie tracker app.
- Responsibilities: Front-end JavaScript, Back-end development, new technologies and project management
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Bootstrap, calorieninja, MVC framework, MySQL, Express.js, Sequelize, Chart.js and Handlebars.js

The Book Club | https://github.com/ajsherrill2/Project-1-Runtime-Terror.git | https://ajsherrill2.github.io/Project-1-Runtime-Terror/

- Created a mobile friendly application that had the ability to easily look up information on books, where they can be bought, and additional information on the book that is relevant to a book reader.
- Responsibilities: Front-end JavaScript, design themes and project management
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Materialize, Google Books REST api, GitHub, LocalStorage

EXPERIENCE

Barista & Cashier 2021 – Present

Summermoon Coffee Cedar Park, TX

 Personable and customer-oriented barista with experience making coffee beverages at cafes. Passionate about fair trade coffee and exotic blends.

Skilled at latte art, multiple espresso machines, and customer service.

Ski Lift Operator 2020 – 2022

Copper Mountain Ski Resort (Winter Season)

Copper Mountain, CO

- Insured the safe operation of mountain chair lifts.
- Provided physical assistance, and reporting to supervisors.
- High level of skiing and snowboarding in order to effectively traverse the mountain.

Contract Lab Technician

2019 - 2020

TxDot Materials Testing Division

Cedar Park. TX

- Prepared, tested, and transferred data for samples, using critical thinking to help make conclusions based on results following consistent best practices.
- Effectively utilize Microsoft Office Suite (Word / Excel / Outlook / PowerPoint) in order to log all data.

Education

Coding Bootcamp Certificate in Full Stack Web Development University of Texas Austin

• A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in Full Stack Web Development.